http://www.b3.net/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last updated in July 27, 2009.
B3.net (“B3”, “we”, or “us”) takes the privacy and protection of your personal information very seriously. By visiting and using our website, or by using any of the services available through the Site, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy describes B3.net's practices with respect to Personal Information and Anonymous Information that we may collect when you use the Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of your Personal Information that is collected by third parties that B3.net does not own or control.
“Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or phone numbers, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. “Anonymous Information” means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy from the users of the Services.
BY USING THE SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE SERVICES, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AS WELL AS OTHER COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY AND BY USING THE SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE SERVICES, YOU ARE EXPRESSLY CONSENTING TO SUCH PROCESSING.
Personal Information We Collect
We only collect the following Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily:
If you register through the Site to receive B3.net updates, we collect your full name and e-mail address When you contact us to learn more about the services, we will collect your name and your e-mail address. When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect any information that is contained in (and/or attached to) your e-mail. Use Of Information We Collect
In general, information (including Personal Information) you submit to us is used by us to provide you and others with the Services, to respond to requests that you make, to improve our Services and to better tailor the features, performance and support of the site.
We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with notifications related to B3.net updates, such as electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, new Product samples, and Product surveys, should you request to receive such communications from us.
Feedback
If you provide feedback about the Services to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We will NEVER sell your Personal Information. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose to or share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.
Choices Regarding Personal Information
We will include unsubscribe instructions in each newsletter or promotional communication you receive from us.
We may send you service-related announcements (such as, but not limited to, notice that we have changed the Services or the Privacy Policy) when we believe it is necessary to do so. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature, but if you do not wish to receive these announcements, you have the option to terminate your status as a B3.net subscriber. You understand that any such termination of your status with B3.net may involve deletion of your Personal Information from our live databases. B3.net will not have any liability whatsoever to you for any termination of your account or related deletion of your information.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us by sending us an e-mail through the website.
